nextag.ca 2016-10-18

# Nextag - Privacy Policy

  1. SCOPE AND CHANGES

Nextag, Inc. and/or our subsidiaries ("Nextag, " "us" or "we") operate the websites [www.nextag.com](http://www.nextag.com/), [www.calibex.com](http://www.calibex.com/) and [www.pricemachine.com](http://www.pricemachine.com/) (we refer to these websites as the "Websites"). This Website Privacy Statement is designed to inform you of the types of information we collect from users, how we use that information, and the circumstances under which we will share it with third parties. This Website Privacy Statement applies only to the Websites. It does not apply to your use of any other websites (whether or not operated by us), including any websites to which we provide links or websites of our partners or advertisers, or to any activities which are not online. Some services referenced in this Privacy Statement are not available on some Websites. Portions of this Website Privacy Statement that pertain to such features or services may not be applicable on each of the Websites.

This Privacy Statement applies to all "users", including those who visit the Websites without being registered. This Website Privacy Statement is effective as of the date listed above. Even if you read and/or agreed to a prior privacy statement, you need to review this updated version. We reserve the right to revise this Website Privacy Statement at any time and at our discretion, as described in this paragraph. If we decide to change our Website Privacy Statement, we will post those changes to this Website Privacy Statement accessible on the homepages of the Websites, and other places we deem appropriate. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users via either email or by posting a notice on the Websites within a reasonable timeframe prior to such use taking effect.

PEOPLE UNDER 18 YEARS OLD  
Our Websites are not intended for use by people under eighteen (18) years of age. If you are under 18, please do not send any information to us. By accessing Websites or using our services, you represent that you are 18 years of age or older.

  2. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE 

This section describes the information that we collect about you and how it is used.

    1. 2.1 Information Submitted by You:

You are not required to provide information about yourself when you visit our Websites but you may elect to do so, such as to take advantage of certain services or features. Examples of situations where you may submit information include:

      * Account or Profile Information: On some of the Websites, you may become a registered user or register for email notices from us. If you do, we ask for some basic contact information, such as a username, ZIP Code and email address. In some cases, as described below, you may enter additional account information. You also may choose to provide other information, either as part of your public profile or otherwise, such as your age, gender or interests.

      * Order Processing Information: We may allow checkout or payment processing features on the Websites to facilitate your purchase of products from merchants. The checkout or payment processing services are provided by a third party service provider, and all sales are made by the merchant. The service provider will collect information that is needed to process the order, such as credit card and related information like your billing address, as well as information that is needed for your order, such as your shipping address and the products that you purchased. This information is transmitted by the service provider to the merchant to complete your order. This information may be collected and stored by the third party service provider and/or the merchant in order to complete these functions. The service provider also may provide us with your contact information (such as name and email address) as well as product purchase information. Our privacy policy will apply to information that we collect or receive, the service provider's privacy policy will apply to information that it collects or receives and the merchant's privacy policy will apply to information that we, our service provider, or you provide to the merchant.

      * Customer Service: You may elect to provide us with information about your purchases, such as customer service requests or information about merchant issues.

      * Content or Correspondence Submitted By You: If you choose to post content on any of the Websites (for example, a product or merchant review, wish list, or comment or discussion forums), or submit personal correspondence to Nextag, we may collect and maintain that information in a file specific to you. Our Websites may also allow you to interact and share personal information and data with others. For example, some of the Websites allow you to create lists of products that are interesting to you. The default for certain lists is for the list to be publicly available. You may change the privacy setting of your lists as provided on the Websites. Additionally, some of the Websites may allow you to share information on social networks, as described in the section "Social Networks".

      * Social Networks: Some of the Websites allow you to register or login to an account you already have with a social networking account, such as Facebook. If you decide to login via a social networking account, we receive information about you from the social networking account, which can include your name, profile picture, email address, gender, user ID, and comments made on the social networking account site. Logging in to our Websites via a social networking account is always optional, but may allow you to publish your activity or interactions with our Websites to your social network account, such as Facebook or Twitter. The information we collect, and the social network's use of any information that you publish to it, may depend on the privacy settings you have with the social networking account or the social network's privacy policy, so be sure to consult your social networking account's privacy settings, and the social networking account's privacy policy and terms of use.

      * Social Media Widgets: Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and Widgets. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

      * Blog: Our Website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [legalnotices@nextag.com](mailto:legalnotices@nextag.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

      * Survey / Contest: We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to improve our site, notify you if you won a contest or to send you an email newsletter or other marketing materials. We use SurveyMonkey a third party service provider to conduct these surveys; that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

      * Links to Third Parties: Our Site includes links to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Nextag. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Website you visit.

    2. 2.2 Automatically Collected Information: Examples of information that may be automatically collected include:
      * Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technology: A cookie is a small file stored on a computer's hard drive or mobile device. We use both "session" cookies, which terminate when a user closes his browser, and "persistent" cookies, which remain on the user's computer until manually deleted. We also may use web beacons (also called clear gifs), which are simple pieces of code that allow us to place small images on web pages or emails, or other standard technology that are similar in function to cookies. We and our partners, affiliates, analytics, or email service providers use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

We use cookies, for example, to save information on your username, ZIP Code and Website preferences, and to collect anonymous information about your use of our Websites and services (including your browsing history, the terms you searched, the products you viewed, your activity on the pages you view, etc.) and your interaction with our advertisements that are served on the Websites or other sites. You may decline our cookies if your web browser software permits, although this may prevent you from accessing certain features on our Websites.

      * Log Files: Log files store information including internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks, and are used to analyze trends, administer the Websites, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not tie log files to personally identifiable information.

      * Local Shared Objects: We use Local Shared Objects, such as Flash cookies and HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use Flash cookies and HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html): 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

    3. 2.3 Information Supplied by Third Parties: We may receive information about you or your use of our or others' websites from other sources, including through the placement of our cookie or similar technology on third party merchant, partner and advertising sites. For example, we may receive product search or purchase information from merchants whose sites you visit after clicking on a product listing on our Website, updated or corrected contact information from third party vendors, credit or related information as part of vendors' fraud detection services (but only with users or merchant's permission to do so), or contact, demographic and other profile information through your interaction with us through social networking accounts, such as Facebook and Twitter (for example, by adding us as a friend on Facebook, following our Twitter account, or engaging in Facebook's "Like" feature). We also may receive or collect similar information from co-branded partners' sites that you visit.
    4. 2.4 Combining Information: We may combine the information that we receive about you from different sources. For example, information about your use of one of our Websites may be combined with information about your use of a different Website or a co-branded partners' site.
  3. USES OF YOUR INFORMATION  

We may use the information that we collect or receive to create a user profile in connection with your account. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences, activities and interactions. We may augment the information that you provide to us with information that we collect about you or information from third parties, as described in this Privacy Statement. The information that we receive about you, including profile information, allows us to provide a number of different services across the Websites and on other sites or applications. For example, we may use: 

    * Your zip code, email address and/or geolocation to provide you with localized services, such as computing TruePrice, which reflects the cost of shipping and sales tax, and matching you with local service providers for some of the matching services we provide (e.g., products, services, deals and/or coupons available locally).

    * Your IP address and/or unique device identifier at times to help identify you as you browse and to gather broad technical and demographic information on who uses our Websites.

    * Your email address to provide you with certain information or updates (such as price alerts, our newsletters, or deals notices) if requested by you and facilitate your provision of product or merchant reviews.

    * The information to manage your account, facilitate the use of certain features of our Websites (e.g., personalized product recommendations, suggestions of content that may be of interest to you, TruePrice prices, submission of product/merchant reviews and creation of your lists) and to send you information about our company, services and products or offers from our partners and advertisers.

    * Information about your use of our Websites and our partners' sites, such as your searches or browsing history, recently viewed items and the products you have purchased, to personalize your experience on the Websites and the search results that we provide you based on your interests, or make recommendations or suggestions to you and to provide you with content and advertising that is more relevant and interesting for you both on our Websites and on third party sites.

    * Anonymous use and browsing information to improve the Websites and our services or third party services such as by analyzing what content or services are helpful or interesting to users, provide better recommendations, perform site optimization, managing content on our Websites by informing us what content and which campaigns are effective, and evaluating the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns.

Anonymous use and browsing information to improve the Websites and our services or third party services such as by analyzing what content or services are helpful or interesting to users, provide better recommendations, perform site optimization, managing content on our Websites by informing us what content and which campaigns are effective, and evaluating the effectiveness of our communications and our marketing campaigns.

    * To contact you regarding the status of your inquiries relating to services or products listed on our Websites or confirm, complete or update your registration or for any other business reason related to your use of our Websites.

    * To contact you regarding account status, changes to this Website Privacy Statement, our Terms of Use or other terms applicable to your use of the Websites.

    * To contact you in response to a customer service question from you, or in relation to any issue arising in respect of the agreement between us and you, or to resolve or attempt to resolve a dispute between users or between us and you.

    * To send related communications regarding, transactions you make using our payment processing service.

    * To improve the experience of using the Websites, improve Nextag's products and services, improve marketing and promotion of our products and services, customize the Websites' content and layout, and generally improve the Websites to meet your needs better.

  4. WHO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. 

Publicly Available Information: Certain information that you provide, such as your lists, is publicly available unless you choose to make it private. You may control the information that is publicly available by signing into your account and adjusting your settings. Additionally, if you choose to activate the setting, some Websites allow you to publish your activity or interactions with our Websites to your social networking account.

Aggregated Information: We aggregate personal information into statistics about users, their usage of the Websites, traffic patterns, and demographics. We may provide third parties, including merchants, partners and advertisers with such statistics, but never in a way that would make the information personally identifiable. This data is aggregated from millions of users who visit the Websites each month.

Anonymous Information: We may provide your anonymous use and browsing information, including the search queries that you enter or products that you view on our site, to third parties, which may include allowing merchants, partners and advertisers, to place cookies and/or web beacons on the Websites and/or clear gifs in our HTML emails to allow third parties to optimize and/or provide you with advertisements that are tailored to your interests.

Merchants and Partners: If you click from the Websites to visit a merchant or other partner, we may provide information about your use of the Websites, such as your search queries, to the merchant or partner, to allow them to provide results that are more tailored to your interests.

Co-Branded Partners: Co-Branded Partners are third parties with whom we may jointly offer a Website, service or feature. We do not collect or share personal information on our co-branded sites. In some instances we utilize framing techniques, which may make it appear that you are on our site when you are actually on a third party website, or may make it appear that you are on a third party website when you are actually on our Website. The privacy policy that governs will be present on these pages so you always know whose privacy practices govern the collection and use of the information that you submit. The Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may apply to its use of your information. 

Service Providers: We may use external service providers to facilitate, improve or outsource elements of our service or operation of the Websites, including processing credit card transactions, sending emails, and providing marketing assistance or analysis. We may provide your information to, or exchange your information with, these service providers for use in their provision of services to us, such as fraud protection and credit risk reduction or marketing analysis. These external service providers may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions or services to us, but may not use it for other purposes. 

Business Transfer and Affiliates: We may share your information with companies that are affiliated with us, that is, are our direct or indirect subsidiaries or parent or sister companies. As we continue to develop our business we might buy or sell companies, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred assets but remains subject to the provisions of any pre-existing privacy statement. In the event that we or substantially all of our assets are acquired, your information may be one of the transferred assets and we may share or assign it with an actual or potential acquirer. 

Legal Requests and Customers' Requests: We may release information from or about you to cooperate with law enforcement officials and third parties to enforce all applicable laws including but not limited to laws relating to intellectual property rights, fraud, and other rights. We also may release information from or about you without a subpoena, court order or other substantially similar legal procedure to law enforcement entities or third parties when we believe release is necessary to comply with the law; to protect our rights, property, or the integrity of the Websites, or the rights or property of our merchants/service providers, customers, users or third parties; or to prevent or investigate illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threat to the physical safety of any person, or violation of our Terms of Use or other agreement between you and us. Further we can (and you authorize us to) disclose information from or about you to consumers who have alleged fraud or any other consumer dispute relating to their transactions and/or communications with you.

Other Trusted Parties: We may provide your contact information and other personal data to trusted third parties so they may provide information to you on products and services that may be of interest to you.

Advertisers: We may share information with advertisers as described in the Interest-Based Advertising section below.

  5. ACCESSING, DELETING AND CHANGING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Registered users can review, update, amend, delete/remove personally identifiable information by signing in using your member name or email address and password, and in some cases, logging in through your social networking account, and then clicking on your "Account" or "Profile" link. Notwithstanding any request from you, we may retain a record of your information that is necessary to comply with applicable law or as necessary to manage your account. To view or change your preferences regarding your use of the Websites and our use of that information, including for the purpose of providing you with advertisements that may be of interest to you, please click [here](http://www.nextag.com/serv/main/buyer/searchPreferences.jsp). For access and changes of any other data, please contact us at [legalnotices@nextag.com](mailto:legalnotices@nextag.com) or the address listed in Section 11 "Contact Us". Upon receipt of your request, which may be subject to identification verification, we will comply with appropriate data correction requests in accordance with applicable law. For access requests, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe upon receiving your request. 

You should also note that if we have provided your information to third parties or if you have allowed third parties to access information through our Websites (such as by publishing your activity and interaction with our Websites to your social networking account, such as Facebook), you will have to make a separate request to them directly if you want to have your information removed from, or corrected in, their databases.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

  6. INTERNET-BASED ADVERTISING

Nextag may display interest-based advertising, also known as personalized or targeted advertising, to you on both the Websites and on unaffiliated sites, using information that we collect when you interact with the Websites or information made available to us by third parties. Please see the section entitled Information Collection and Use for more information on the types of information we gather, including from third parties, which allow us to provide you with more useful and relevant ads. We do not provide personally identifiable information to advertisers or third party sites that display our ads. We also may provide information about your use of the Websites to advertising partners to allow them to show you more relevant advertisements on their sites or in their advertising networks. 

Some of the advertisements that appear on the Websites are delivered or served to you by third-party Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"). These companies use certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and also use cookies, clear gifs or similar methods to collect information, such as anonymous data about your visit to and use of the Websites and your interactions with their advertisements. These companies may use this information and information that they have collected from other websites to provide you with advertisements that are tailored to your interests. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that these companies may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party Websites are not covered by this Website Privacy Statement. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

The [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.aboutads.info/) offers useful information about Internet advertising companies including information about how to opt-out of their information collection practices. To receive further information or to opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/index.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

  7. CHOICE / OPT OUT POLICY

Email: We understand you may not want to receive promotional email from us. You can choose to opt out of receiving promotional email communications by: 

Clicking [here](http://www.nextag.com/serv/main/emailcampaign/optout.jsp) if you are a registered user.

Email us at [optout@nextag.com](mailto:optout@nextag.com).

Click the appropriate unsubscribe link contained within the email that you receive. 

Please note that opting out may prevent you from receiving email regarding updates and improvements to the Websites or offers and promotions that may interest you.

In some cases you have the option to submit personal information in order to forward this information to our partners that have products or services in which you may be interested. In the event we share this information with our partners (e.g., service providers), we no longer have control over the use of such information and your rights regarding such use will be governed by the policies of our partners. You will then have to contact them directly with any opt-out request.

Advertising Preferences: We may collect information about your interaction with our advertisements by using advertising cookies. We may also allow advertising partners to record that you have visited the Websites to allow us to provide you with relevant advertising on the partners' sites. To opt-out of our advertising cookies or partner advertising cookies, please click [here](http://www.nextag.com/serv/deal/serv/main/buyer/help/AdTargetingOptOut.jsp).

Personalization Preferences: To change your preferences regarding your search and browsing history and our use of that information, including providing you with advertisements that may be of interest to you, please click [here](https://www.nextag.com/accounts/privacy).

  8. SECURITY MEASURES TO PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The security and confidentiality of your information is very important to us. We have implemented reasonable technical, administrative, and physical security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access and improper use during transmission and once it’s received. We review our security procedures on a regular basis to consider new or updated and appropriate technology and methods. However, no method of transmission of information over the Internet, or method of electronic storage of information, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

It is important that you use a strong password and protect your password from unauthorized use. 

  9. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits residents of California who use our service for private, family or household purposes to request certain standard information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes (including a list of categories of data disclosed in the previous calendar year and names and addresses of data recipients). To make such a request, please contact us as provided below.

  10. INTERNET CRIME COMPLAINT CENTER

Nextag wants your Internet surfing experience to be safe. Help protect yourself. If you believe you have been a victim of Internet crime you can file a complaint with the Internet Crime Complaint Center (IC3), a partnership between the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the National White Collar Crime Center. Their website is [http://www.ic3.gov/](http://www.ic3.gov/default.aspx). 

  11. CHOICE / OPT OUT POLICY

Email: We understand you may not want to receive promotional email from us. You can choose to opt out of receiving promotional email communications by: 

  12. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Website Privacy Statement, the practices of the Websites, or your use of the Websites, please contact us at:

Privacy Officer  
Nextag Inc.  
555 Twin Dolphin Drive\\\  
Suite 370  
Redwood City, CA 94065  
legalnotices@nextag.com
